insidethehall.com 2018-11-25

# Inside the Hall Privacy Policy - Inside the Hall | Indiana Hoosiers Basketball News, Recruiting and Analysis

This is the Web site of Inside the Hall. We can be reached via e-mail at [insidethehall@gmail.com](mailto:insidethehall@gmail.com). By accessing the Inside the Hall Web site or using the services offered by Inside the Hall you agree and acknowledge to be bound by our Privacy Policy.

Inside the Hall knows that you care about how your personal information is used and shared, and we take your privacy very seriously. Please read the following to learn more about our Privacy Policy. By visiting our website, you are accepting the practices outlined in this Privacy Policy.

This Privacy Policy covers Inside the Hall’s treatment of personal information that Inside the Hall gathers when you are on the Inside the Hall website and when you use Inside the Hall services. This policy does not apply to the practices of third parties that Inside the Hall does not own or control, or to individuals that Inside the Hall does not employ or manage.

**Information Collected by Inside the Hall**

We only collect personal information that is relevant to the purpose of our website. This information allows us to provide you with a customized and efficient experience. We do not process this information in a way that is incompatible with this objective. We collect the following types of information from our Inside the Hall users:

1\. Information You Provide to Us: We receive and store any information you enter on our website or provide to us in any other way. You can choose not to provide us with certain information, but then you may not be able to take advantage of many of our special features.

2\. Automatic Information: We receive and store certain types of information whenever you interact with us. Inside the Hall and its authorized agents automatically receive and record certain “traffic data” on their server logs from your browser including your IP address, Inside the Hall cookie information, and the page you requested. Inside the Hall uses this traffic data to help diagnose problems with its servers, analyze trends and administer the website. Inside the Hall may collect and, on any page, display the total counts that page has been viewed.

Many companies offer programs that help you to visit websites anonymously. While Inside the Hall will not be able to provide you with a personalized experience if we cannot recognize you, we want you to be aware that these programs are available.

3. We use third-party advertising companies to serve ads when you visit our Web site. These companies may use aggregated information (not including your name, address, email address or telephone number) about your visits to this and other Web sites in order to provide advertisements about goods and services of interest to you. For further information, consult the privacy policies of our partners, which are linked below:

Google – <https://policies.google.com/technologies/ads>  
Teads – <https://teads.tv/privacy-policy/>  
Connatix – <https://www.connatix.com/privacy-policy/>  
Nativo – <https://www.nativo.com/privacy-policy/>  
Sovrn – <https://www.sovrn.com/privacy-policy/>  
Neulion – [https://www.neulion.com/ViewArticle.dbml?DB_LANG=C&DB_OEM_ID=30000&ATCLID=211671311](https://www.neulion.com/ViewArticle.dbml?DB_LANG=C&DB_OEM_ID=30000&ATCLID=211671311)  
Outbrain – <https://www.outbrain.com/legal/>

4. You are required to provide a valid email address to disqus.com in order to comment and participate on Inside the Hall. You can read the privacy policy for disqus.com by [clicking here](https://www.disqus.com/privacy-policy/). Inside the Hall does not maintain any email lists and will only email users of our site if we are contacted by the user first.

5\. Inside the Hall uses the services of Quantcast and Google Analytics to track traffic to our website. For more information on what information is collected by Quantcast and Google Analytics, please consult their privacy policies, linked below:

<https://www.quantcast.com/privacy/>  
<https://support.google.com/analytics/answer/6004245?hl=en>

**E-mail Communications**

Inside the Hall is very concerned about your privacy and we will never provide your email address to a third party without your explicit permission, as detailed in the “Sharing Your Information” section below. Inside the Hall may send out e-mails with Inside the Hall -related news, products, offers, surveys or promotions.

**Cookies**

Cookies are alphanumeric identifiers that we transfer to your computer’s hard drive through your Web browser to enable our systems to recognize your browser and tell us how and when pages in our website are visited and by how many people. Inside the Hall cookies do not collect personal information, and we do not combine information collected through cookies with other personal information to tell us who you are or what your screen name or e-mail address is.

The “help” portion of the toolbar on the majority of browsers will direct you on how to prevent your browser from accepting new cookies, how to command the browser to tell you when you receive a new cookie, or how to fully disable cookies. We recommend that you leave the cookies activated because cookies allow you to use many of Inside the Hall’s features.

Inside the Hall’s advertising partners may place a cookie on your browser that makes it possible to collect anonymous non-personally identifiable information that ad delivery systems use to present more relevant ads. If you would prefer to opt-out of this standard practice, please visit our advertising partner privacy policies and opt-out pages, which are linked in the previous sections.

**Sharing Your Information**

Rest assured that we neither rent nor sell your personal information to anyone and that we will share your personal information only as described below.

Inside the Hall Personnel: Inside the Hall personnel and authorized consultants and/or contractors may have access to user information if necessary in the normal course of Inside the Hall business.

Business Transfers: In some cases, we may choose to buy or sell assets. In these types of transactions, user information is typically one of the business assets that is transferred. Moreover, if Inside the Hall, or substantially all of its assets, were acquired, user information would be one of the assets that is transferred.

Protection of Inside the Hall and Others: We may release personal information when we believe in good faith that release is necessary to comply with a law; to enforce or apply our Terms of Use and other policies; or to protect the rights, property, or safety of Inside the Hall, our employees, our users, or others. This includes exchanging information with other companies and organizations for fraud protection and credit risk reduction.

Syndication: Inside the Hall allows for the RSS syndication of all of its public content within the Inside the hall website.

With Your Consent: Except as noted above, we will contact you when your personal information is shared with third parties or used for a purpose incompatible with the purpose(s) for which it was originally collected, and you will be able to opt out to prevent the sharing of this information.

**Children Under 18 Years of Age**

You must be 13 years and older to register to use the Inside the Hall website. As a result, Inside the Hall does not specifically collect information about children. If we learn that Inside the Hall has collected information from a child under the age of 13, we will delete that information as quickly as possible.We recommend that minors between the ages of 13 and 18 ask and receive their parents’ permission before using Inside the Hall or sending information about themselves or anyone else over the Internet.

**Changes to this Privacy Policy**

Inside the Hall may amend this Privacy Policy from time to time, at its sole discretion. Use of information we collect now is subject to thePrivacy Policy in effect at the time such information is used. If we make changes to the Privacy Policy, we will notify you by posting an announcement on the Inside the Hall website so you are always aware of what information we collect, how we use it, and under what circumstances if any, it is disclosed.

**Effective Date of this Privacy Policy**

This Privacy Policy is effective as of 5/24/18 and last updated 5/24/18.
